New York State Board of Mediation Cases 5581
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- A 6078 - A 6269 and 1/45-1 to 5/46-8 (1945-46). (Box 28)
  - Hotel McAlpin Pharmacy, Inc., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Milk Dealers' Association of Metropolitan New York, Inc., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Huson-American Corp., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Weil Furniture Co., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Roof Athletic Club, Inc., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Superior Meter Co., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - New York Quinine and Chemical Works, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - 2402 65th Street Corp., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Nicholas Shoe Rebuilders, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Yates, Dr. E.L., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Le Coq Rouge, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Selectar Mfg. Corp., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Piser and Company, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - G.M. Co. Manufacturing, Inc., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Krasne, A., Inc., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Magna Products Corp., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Preston, Mel, Shoe, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Ronzoni Macaroni Co., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Unique Balance Company, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - United States Trucking Corp., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Purity Bakeries, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Everybody's Tool and Die Corp., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Ovington Gift Shop, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Janaug, Inc., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Cohn, Sigmunc and Co., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Muller Dairy, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - 2925 Matthews Avenue and 2922 Barnes Avenue, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Zeregas, A. and Sons, Inc., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Sun Chemical Corp., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Beedy, Z. and Co., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Wander Iron Works, Inc., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Hospital Supply and Wattars Laboratories, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Radio Wire Television Inc., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Fingold, Henry and Co., Inc., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - Namm, A.I. and Sons, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - Premier Metal Etching Co., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - Cutler-Hammer, Inc., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - Machinery Builders Inc., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - Gordon Baking Co., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - Krasne Bros., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 54)
  - Schoonmaker, A.O. Insulation Co., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 55)
  - Luxor Luncheonette, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 56)
  - Ross Galvanizing Works, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 57)
  - Masell Mfg. Co., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 58)
  - United Parcel Service Co., of N.Y., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 59)
  - A.O. Schoonmaker Insulation Co., Inc., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 60)
  - Fairacres Farms, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 61)
  - Picker-Linz Importers, Inc., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 62)
  - Merit Farms, Inc., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 63)
  - Kollsman Instrument Company, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 64)
  - New York State Railways (J. Largay), 1945 (Box 28, Folder 65)
  - Semer Hardware Co., Inc., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 66)
  - Imperial Hotel, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 67)
  - Messing Bakeries, Inc., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 68)
  - Le Cody Toasted Pies, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 69)
  - Box Novelties Company, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 70)
  - East Side Chevrolet Company, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 71)
  - The French Pavilion Restaurant Corp., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 72)
  - Peerless Importers, Inc., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 73)
  - J. Cane and Sons, Inc., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 74)
  - Curry, B.F. Co., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 75)
  - Henry Fingold Co., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 76)
  - Automatic Range Company, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 77)
  - S.S. White Dental Mfg. Co., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 78)
  - D. and W. Metal Products Co., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 79)
  - Sordoni Construction Company, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 80)
  - Childs Company, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 81)
  - Gates Ambulance and Oxygen Service, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 82)
  - Pressman, Jack and Co., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 83)
  - Shelter Island Oyster Co., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 84)
  - Banner Smoked Fish Corp., 1946 (Box 28, Folder 85)
  - Le Cody Toasted Pies, Inc., 1946 (Box 28, Folder 86)
  - Standard Coated Products, Inc., 1946 (Box 28, Folder 87)
  - S and W Poultry Co., 1946 (Box 28, Folder 88)
  - Childs Company, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 89)
  - Fairmount Iron Works, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 90)
  - Lubin's Bar and Grill, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 91)
- A 6272 - A 6597 (1946). (Box 29)
  - House wrecking Contractors, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Brooklyn Eagle, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 3, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Olympic Pharmacy, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Book Publishers Shipping Service, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Premier Metal Etching Co., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Thomas, S.B. Co., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Eton Pharmacy, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Up-to-Date Candy Co., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Associated Foundries and Mfg. Co., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Beer, William J., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Fenway Realty Corp., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Keller Dorian Corp., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Superior Meter Co., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Schenectady Railway Company, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Glass, H. and H. and Bro., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Macy, R.H. and Co., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Vocational Foundation Inc. for Young Men and Young Women, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Fair Trade Merchandise Company, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Spear and Company, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Cohn, Sigmund and Co., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Andrews and Perillo Company, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - New York Amsterdam News, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Palace Theatre, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Reuben's Restaurant, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Sunland Beverage Corp., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Students Drug Shop, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Champion Aero Metal Products, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Associated Wreckers, Inc., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Klotz, J Inc., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Diamond and Cooperberg, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Lew's Pants Shop, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Phoenix Finishing Shop, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Acme Brass Co., Inc., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Ward Leonard Electric Company, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Electromatic Mfg. Corp., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Federal Steel Rule Die, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Ebling Brewing Company, Inc., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Editorial Publications, Inc., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - American Air Lines, Inc., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - 1911 Albemarle Road, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Army and Navy Stores, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Sophia and Co., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - Volk, Albert A. Co., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - 730 - 740 Grand Concourse, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - Eagle Electric Mfg. Co., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - Fischer, Chas. Spring Co., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - Optical Service Inc., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - Breakstone Bros., Inc., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - Plazmont Pharmacy, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 50)
  - Champion Aero Metal Products, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - Cohn, Sigmund and Co., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 52)
  - United Parcel Service, Inc., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 53)
  - Esco Iron Works, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 54)
  - Pathe Engineering Co., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 55)
  - Henshaw Furniture Co., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 56)
  - 3025 Godwin Terrace, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 57)
  - Jewel Sheen Waterproofing Corp., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 58)
  - North American Philips Co., Inc., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 59)
  - Zamax Mfg. Co., Inc., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 60)
  - Atlantic Macaroni Co., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 61)
  - Baumann, C. Ludwig, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 62)
  - Tarr, Edward, Inc., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 63)
  - Swiss Radium and Dial Painting Co., Inc., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 64)
  - Namm, A.I. and Sons, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 65)
  - Nathan Mfg. Co., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 66)
  - Trio Drug Co., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 67)
  - 110 West 40th Street, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 68)
  - Childs Company, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 69)
  - New York Furniture Merchants Assn., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 70)
  - Dreyer Bros. Home Furnishing Corp., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 71)
  - Marxman Products Co., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 72)
  - Fenster, I. and Sons, Inc., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 73)
  - Ideal Leather Novelty Co., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 74)
  - ] Baking Co., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 75)
  - Holtite Shoe Repair Co., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 76)
  - Rokeach, I. and Sons, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 77)
  - Ace Ice Cream Cabinet Co., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 78)
  - Formfitting Slipper Co., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 79)
  - Gold Seal Cedar Chest and Novelty Corp., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 80)
  - Dutch Masters Paints and Varnish Co., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 81)
  - Clarostat Mfg. Co., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 82)
  - American Stamp Co., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 83)
  - Third Avenue Transit Corp., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 84)
- A 6603 - A 6899 (1946). (Box 30)
  - Longchamps Restaurant, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Par-Metal Products Corp., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Assn. of Wholesale Food Merchants, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Modell's, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - 1014 Gerard Avenue, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Breakstone Bros, Inc., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - 205 East 42nd Street, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - A. Mascioli and Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - National Electronics Mfg. Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Coh-ler Corp., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Polk, Chas Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Watch Motor Mainspring Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - National Exhibition Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Borden's Farm Products, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - California Pie and Baking Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Rose Frame and Mirror Works, Inc., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Koppers Company, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - M and H Food Products, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Reuben, Arnold, Inc., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - International Mutoscope Corp., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Queens Borough Gas and Electric Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Marlow Floral Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Nathan Mfg. Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - North Shore Bus Co., Inc., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Pan American Airways, Inc., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Queens-Nassau Transit Lines, Inc., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Beer, William J. Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - New York Quinine and Chemical Works, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Ronzoni Macaroni Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Hotel Sharon, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Radio City Products, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Associated Foundry and Manufacturers. Inc., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Buffalo Radio Stations, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Janaug, Inc., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - La Planta Cigar Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Maxim Plastics, Inc., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Gottfried Baking Co., Inc., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Moeller Instrument Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Portchester Iron Works, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - 125 Brighton 11th Street, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Hardman, Peck and Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - Royal Switchboard Co., Inc., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - Heide, Henry Inc., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - Hugo Brand Tannery, Inc., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - Lipco Drug Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - Siegel, Sidney, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - Solar Furniture Craftsmen, Inc., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - Schindel Mercantile Co., Inc., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 48)
  - New Yorker Pharmacy, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 49)
  - Plumbing and Heating Wholesalers Employers Assn., Inc., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 50)
  - Title Guaranty and Trust, Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 51)
  - 65-67 East 175th Street, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 52)
  - 2427 Webster Avenue, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 53)
  - North American Iron and Steel Co., Inc., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 54)
  - 1225 Seneca Avenue, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 55)
  - Benjamin Franklin Hotel, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 56)
  - Cohn, Sigmund and Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 57)
  - Hotel Luxor, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 58)
  - Lambui, John W., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 59)
  - Mackay Radio Telegraph Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 60)
  - S and W Fine Foods, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 61)
  - Modern Refrigerator Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 62)
  - Reichhold Chemical Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 63)
  - Brewer Dry Dock Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 64)
  - Purity Bakeries, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 65)
  - Scully Walton Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 66)
  - Boerum Paper Box Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 67)
  - Continental Baking Co., Inc., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 68)
  - Evy Footwear Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 69)
  - Levy, H.S. Baking Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 70)
  - Vogel, S. Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 71)
  - Cooper's Radio and Sporting Goods, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 72)
  - Box Novelties Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 73)
  - 1650 West Tenth Street, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 74)
  - New York Quinine and Chemical Works, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 75)
  - Remington Optical Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 76)
  - 2824 Morris Avenue, et al., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 77)
  - Delia Waste Products Corp., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 78)
  - Nolan Motors, Inc., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 79)
  - 1454 University Avenue, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 80)
  - Eastern Plating Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 81)
  - Longchamps Restaurants, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 82)
  - Allen Recording Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 83)
  - American Package Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 84)
  - Hotel Willard, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 85)
  - Sievering, Philip, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 86)
  - Gimbel Brothers, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 87)
  - 1385 Shakespeare Avenue, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 88)
  - Bridge Hardware Co., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 89)
  - National Backing Corp., 1946 (Box 30, Folder 90)
  - Consumers Cooperative, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 91)
- A 6900- A 7199 (1946). (Box 31)
  - Lincoln Wire Co., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Metropolitan Bakery and Luncheonette Assn, Inc., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - New York Quinine and Chemical Works, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - B and L Drugs, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Brighton Beach Mattress Co., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Berkman and Marder, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Olympic Pharmacy, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Cameo Beauty Salon of Brooklyn, Inc., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Lane Bryant Inc., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - 333 86th St., Brooklyn, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Queens County Master Barbers Assn., Chapter 4, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Union Health Center, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Drosness Pharmacy, et al, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Philips Laboratories, Inc., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - S and S Drapery Co., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Wolta Electrical Products Corp., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Henshaw Furniture Co., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Barbara, Sam Co., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Corona Industries Ltd., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Nathan Mfg. Co., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Thomas, S.B., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Garrett and Company, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Gross Trucking Co., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Leumas Ware Corp., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Mayflower Transit Lines, Inc., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Yates, Dr. E.L., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Plumbing and Heating Wholesalers Assn., Inc., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Bloomingdale Bros., Inc., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Model Footwear Co., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - 2067 Harrison Avenue, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Retail Apparel Merchants Assn., Inc., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Longchamps Restaurants, Inc., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Benlee Sporting Goods Co., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Romillion Restaurant, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Saymont Optical Co., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - Bronx County Pharmaceutical Assn., Inc., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - De Luxe Mattress Co., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - Seaporcel-Porcelain, Inc., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - Bloomingdale Bros., Inc., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - Par-Metal Corporation, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - Royal Novelty Co., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - Tanen Shop, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - 3025-27 Godwin Terrace, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 43)
  - D.I. Brass Turning Works, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 44)
  - Allied Gymnasium Equipment Co., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 45)
  - Bradmore Footwear Inc., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 46)
  - Fischer, Chas. Spring Co., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 47)
  - Frazer and Jones Co., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 48)
  - Longchamps Restaurants, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 49)
  - National House and Window Cleaning Co., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 50)
  - Ward Baking Co., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 51)
  - Metalab Equipment Co., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 52)
  - Mica Manufacturing Co., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 53)
  - Press Wireless, Inc., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 54)
  - Schwab Bros. and Baer, Inc., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 55)
  - Namm, A.I. and Sons, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 56)
  - Crawford Clothes, Inc., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 57)
  - Duroyd Gasket Co., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 58)
  - Grand Avenue Baking Co., Inc., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 59)
  - S. Modern Stamping Co., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 60)
  - Cleaning Contractors Corp., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 61)
  - S. Hochhouser, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 62)
  - Ardee Plastics, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 63)
  - Everybody's Tool and Die Corp., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 64)
  - Par Metal Products Corp., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 65)
  - United Parcel Service Inc., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 66)
  - American Insignia Co., Inc., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 67)
  - Electromatic Manufacturing Co., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 68)
  - Yates, E.L. Dr., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 69)
  - National Electro Plating Co., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 70)
  - New Era Dental Laboratory, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 71)
  - Henry I. Siegel Co., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 72)
  - Stuart Dean Company, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 73)
  - Winston Slipper Company, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 74)
  - 2440 Amsterdam Avenue, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 75)
  - Lunenfeld, Dr. Julius, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 76)
  - Order Bros. and Schreiber, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 77)
  - Patchogue-Plymouth Mills Corp., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 78)
  - Union's Exhibits, Columbia University, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 79)
  - Warner's Bros. Pictures Inc., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 80)
  - Singer Sewing Machine Co., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 81)
  - Union News Co., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 82)
  - Assoc. Foundries and Manufacturers, Inc., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 83)
  - Union News Co., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 84)
  - D.I. Brass Turning Works, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 85)
  - Yorkville Restaurants and Cabarets Owners Association, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 86)
  - Abott Transformer Company, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 87)
  - Electronic Devices Corporation, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 88)
- A 7200 - A 7522 (1946-47). (Box 32)
  - Swiss American Watch Hospital, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Title Guarantee and Trust Company, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - American Type Founders, Inc., 1946 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Harjer Furniture Company, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Klein Piano Company, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Longchamps, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Milton, Geo. A. Can Company, Inc., 1946 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Progressive Restaurant Owners Association, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Cardinal Parfums, Inc., 1946 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Infant and Juvenile Manufacturers. Assn. Inc., 1946 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Service Backing Corporation, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Moeller Instrument Co., 1946 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Murray and Sorrenson Company, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - National Electronics Mfg. Company, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - 421 West 28th St. Corporation, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - American Wine Association, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Kelton Cosmetic Company, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Rabinowe, E. and Co., 1946 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Stop-Motion Devices Corporation, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Canada Dry Ginger Ale, Inc., 1946 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Olympia Provision and Baking Co., Inc., 1946 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Gottfried Baking Co., Inc., 1946 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Godners, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - R.K. Backing Corp., 1946 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Master Electro-plating Assn., Inc., 1946 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Purity Bakeries, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - General Bronze Corp., 1946 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Cineffects, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Liquidometer Corp., 1946 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Berkman Bros., 1946 (Box 32, Folder 30)
- A 7524 - A 7814 (1947). (Box 33)
  - Plazmont Pharmacy, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Randall Cadillac Corp., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Chelsea Paper Box Co., 1946 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Star Cut Rate Variety Store, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Midtown Realty Owners Association Inc., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Economy Drug, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Hertz Pharmacy, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Israel Popelowksy, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Astor Ramel Mfg. Co., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - JK Sebo and Co., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Nathan Mfg. Co., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Brout Credit Jewelers, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Butler, HJ & Bros Inc., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Cambridge Instrument Co., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Caviar Restaurant, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Champion Aero Metal Producers, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - DI Brass Turning Works, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Lincoln Wire Co., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Jack Vogel, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Wesco Wire Goods Co., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Singer Mfg. Co., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Sosna Bros., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Wood Container Co, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Louis Cottin Co., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Ille Electric Corp, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - De Jur-AMSCO Corp., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - New York Water Service Corp., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Bijur Lubricating Co., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Caf Romillon Co., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - General Bronze Corporation, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Gnome Inc., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Kay Mfg. Corp., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - A. Kramer and Co., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Pugsley Cut Rate Pharmacy, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - B and L Drugs, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Blue Print Co. Inc., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Dictograph Sales Corp., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Ormont Drug and Chemical Co., Inc., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Snug Bar and Grill, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Standard Switchboard Co., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - Fifth Street, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - United Parcel Service, Inc., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - American Dental Laboratory, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - Cardinal Parfums, Inc., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 44)
  - Cake and Pastry Employers, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - Abko Products, Inc., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 46)
  - Consolidated Cork Corp., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 47)
  - De Luxe Bar and Restaurant Equipment Co., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 48)
  - Certified Pharmacal Co., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 49)
  - Childs Co., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 50)
  - National Reconditioning Co., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 51)
  - Liquidometer Corp., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 52)
  - Progressive Restaurant Owners Association, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 53)
  - Ludwig Bauman, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 54)
  - Alltite Motor Products Co., Inc., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 55)
  - Acme Brass Co., Inc., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 56)
  - QOS Corporation, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 57)
  - Hanscom Baking Corp., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 58)
  - New York Stock Exchange, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 59)
  - Jacob Rabinowitz and Co., Inc., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 60)
  - Title Guarantee and Trust Co., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 61)
  - Standard Brands, Inc., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 62)
  - Textile Fabric Co., Inc., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 63)
  - 1350 East 18th Street, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 64)
  - Century Desk Co., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 65)
  - Bloomingdale Bros., Inc., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 66)
  - Canada Dry Ginger Ale Co., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 67)
  - Diamond Processing, Inc., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 68)
  - Radio Wire and Television Co., 1947 (Box 33, Folder 69)